Anna Meudec

+353851845207 | 274 North Circular Road, Highfield Park, Dublin 7 | annameudec88@gmail.com | LinkedIn

Career Objective

Highly driven final-year student currently pursuing my Bachelor's in International Business. Experienced in independent and team projects with over 3 years experience in customer service. Seeking an opportunity to apply my skills and passion for analytics to enhance customer-centric solutions.

Skills

Technical Skills: Python | SQL | Power BI | Tableau | Excel | Git | Microsoft Office | Google Suite **Professional Skills:** Business Strategy | Operations Management | Critical Thinking | Data Analytics | Global Business Environment | Changing Consumers | Cross-Functional Teams **Languages:** English (Native) | Spanish (B2) | French (B1)

Education

Dublin City University, Ireland

2020 - 2024

BA in International Business (Spain) with a specialisation in Business Analytics.

- Expected BA Result: First Class Honours (I.I)
- Relevant Modules: Data Mining and Predictive Analytics, Workflow and Data Management for Business Analytics, Managing Change and Digital Transformation, Professional Business Analytics Portfolio
- Achievements: Ranked 1st overall in BA International Business 2022

University of Valencia, Spain

September 2022 - June 2023

Third-year integrated year abroad program, marked by an immersive experience and instruction exclusively in Spanish.

- End of Year Result: Pass with Honours
- Modules: Strategic Management, Commercial Distribution, International Management,
 International Marketing, Spanish Language for Business, Advanced Spanish Language Skills

St. Leo's College, Co. Carlow

2014 - 2020

- Irish Leaving Certificate: 498 Points
- Achievements: St. Leo's College Full Attendance Award 2015, Meitheal Leader 2018, 3rd Place in The Junior Certificate Technology Project Regional Finals

Work Experience

Residence Assistant

Yugo, Dublin

- Facilitated the creation and modification of bookings for students enrolled in full-year academic stays.
- Led the company's customer service efforts by engaging with customers on Livechat and various social media platforms to organise, pursue and secure sales.
- Orchestrated virtual and in-person tours for students and their parents, ensuring a comprehensive and informative experience.
- Functioned as a critical support system for students, addressing their individual needs and concerns.
- Oversaw the coordination of social events and the planning of activities aimed at enhancing student well-being.
- Designed and executed social media marketing campaigns to promote all Yugo properties across
 Dublin and Cork.

Retail Sales Assistant

Next Retail Ltd., Carlow

December 2017 - January 2019

- Supported customers with their purchases and inquiries.
- Collaborated with team members to achieve customer satisfaction targets and sales objectives.
- Oversaw merchandise displays and store layouts to improve customer engagement.
- Managed stockroom duties, including tagging merchandise, organising inventory, and conducting regular inventory checks.
- Participated in training and development programs to enhance product knowledge and retail sales techniques.

Waitress

Bake Cafe, Carlow

September 2017 - January 2018

- Assisted with the opening and closing duties, including setup, cleaning and restocking the kitchen.
- Delivered attentive and personable customer service to all customers.
- Managed credit and cash transactions as well as the handling of customer returns.
- Successfully completed The Matthew Algie Barista Coffee Course (2017) through company training.

Interests

In my personal life, I have a strong passion for learning languages and experiencing new cultures through travel. I also have a keen interest in interior design and love researching new ideas for my home. Additionally, I have recently begun attending yoga classes in my local area and have really enjoyed meeting new people and socialising in a more laid-back environment.

References

References are available upon request.